<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>linux on Ken Moini</title>
    <link>https://www.kenmoini.com/tags/linux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in linux on Ken Moini</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 22:31:48 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.kenmoini.com/tags/linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick n’ Dirty – Adding disks to Proxmox with LVM</title>
      <link>https://www.kenmoini.com/blog/quick-n-dirty-adding-disks-to-proxmox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 22:31:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kenmoini.com/blog/quick-n-dirty-adding-disks-to-proxmox/</guid>
      <description>Proxmox LVM Expansion, adding additional disks to your Proxmox host for VM storage. No real story behind this post, just something simple and probably more of a documentation of the process for myself more than anything.
In case you were just CRAVING the story and background behind this…well, I recently got a few new (to me) Dell R710 servers, pretty decked out. Booting Proxmox off of a 128gb USB 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Defined Networking with Linux</title>
      <link>https://www.kenmoini.com/blog/software-defined-networking-with-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 22:31:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kenmoini.com/blog/software-defined-networking-with-linux/</guid>
      <description>Well well well, it’s been a while y’all.
Been busy developing and writing a few things, some more exciting stuff coming up in the pipeline. A lot of the projects I’m working on have to kind of sort of “plug together” and to do a lot of this I use open-source solutions and a lot of automation. Today I’d like to show you how to setup a Linux based router, complete with packet forwarding, DHCP, DNS, and dare I even say NTP!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wrangling Bluetooth in RHEL &amp; CentOS 7</title>
      <link>https://www.kenmoini.com/blog/wrangling-bluetooth-on-rhel-and-centos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 22:31:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kenmoini.com/blog/wrangling-bluetooth-on-rhel-and-centos/</guid>
      <description>I recently started as the Lead Solution Architect at Fierce Software. It’s been an excellent experience so far and I’m excited to be working with such a great team. At Fierce Software we help Public Sector entities find enterprise ready open source solutions. Our portfolio of vendors is deliberately diverse because in today’s enterprise multi-vendor, multi-vertical solutions are commonplace. No one’s running all Cisco network gear, Cisco servers, annnnd then what’s after that?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>